<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DaanCorona</string>
    <string name="MAP_API_KEY" translatable="false">AIzaSyCiyc_4v8hbbwX86H6Cy9020JNY6dzQJGE</string>
    <string name="hindi">हिन्दी</string>
    <string name="english">अंग्रेज़ी</string>
    <string name="select_a_language">Select language / भाषा चुने :</string>
    <string name="mouDetails1">This Memorandum of Understanding (referred to as the “MoU”) establishes the terms for collaboration between:\n
      “DaanCorona”: includes the mobile application, online web-application and the essence of the service being offered (referred to as the “app” or “platform” or “service”), and \n •
    </string>
    <string name="mouDetails2">
        includes the business and the businesses’ stakeholders - owners, employees, and the like (referred to as the “business”) \n
for the purpose of signing-up on the DaanCorona platform and the following is being agreed upon by the undersigned.\n\n
        A. Duration:\n
Once accepted by business signing onto the platform, through the app, this Memorandum of Understanding shall take effect from
    </string>
    <string name="mouDetails3">
         and shall stay in effect for a period of 2 years. This Memorandum of Understanding is at-will and thus may be modified with the mutual consent of competent authorities from both parties. Thus the duration of the Memorandum of Understanding may be extended or reduced with mutual consent.\n\n

B. Deliverables from DaanCorona to the business:\n
 • After the signing of this Memorandum of Understanding, DaanCorona shall be promising these deliverables:\n
 • A public profile for the business on the platform.\n
 • Publicly display the business’s profile to customers on the website.\n
 • Allow customers to buy vouchers in the said business’ name. \n
 • Ability to limit the sale of the vouchers by way of a ‘Maximum credit’ amount, decided by the business during registration. \n
 • Transfer funds to the business’s bank account (details mentioned in the registration process) equivalent to the amounts received from the sale of the vouchers, minus a transaction fee equal to the transaction fee charged by the DaanCorona website’s payment gateway and any other fees charged by external sources.\n
 • The following details shall be conveyed, through the mobile application - Total monetary compensation received, the monetary value of vouchers issued, the monetary value of vouchers redeemed.\n\n


C. Deliverables from the business to DaanCorona:\n
 • A guarantee to honour the vouchers issued through DaanCorona to the customers, for a period of one year.\n
 • A guarantee to allow customers to pay using DaanCorona issued vouchers on all services, goods, products or any other deliverables offered by the business to the customers when the situation regarding COVID-19 has improved and the business resumes operations. \n
 • The business admits that and bears a promise that any information provided in the registration process or by any form of communication thereafter, is accurate and that the business carries relevant proof for this in the form of government identification, business-related registration documents, or any other relevant, verifiable, and legal document.\n
 • The business agrees that it shall bear any and all responsibility for any disputes, refund claims, and other customer issues regarding the redemption and fulfilment of the vouchers issued through DaanCorona. It also understands that DaanCorona shall limit its responsibility and liability, fully, in this regard. \n
 • A guarantee to solve all relevant queries from customers (directed to them by DaanCorona or the customers directly) regarding the fulfilment and redemption of the vouchers, as soon as possible. The responsibility for any complications arising from the business’ inability to do so, shall remain with the business. \n
 • The business agrees that DaanCorona may stop offering its services partially, or in full, without any notice. \n
 • The business agrees and shall comply with all conditions stated in the following documents - The Terms of Service/ Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Refund Policy, and any others that are updated on the platform at a later date. The responsibility for checking for any updates in any of the above-mentioned documents shall also be borne by the business.\n
 • An understanding that any non-compliance with above-mentioned conditions shall be grounds for strict and immediate action - legal, or otherwise.\n\n\n
Date:
    </string>

<string name="mouDethin1">
     "DaanCorona": इसमें मोबाइल एप्लिकेशन, ऑनलाइन वेब-एप्लिकेशन और दी जा रही सेवा का सार ("एप्लिकेशन" या "प्लेटफ़ॉर्म" या "सेवा") और \ n
</string>
    <string name="personal_info">व्यक्तिगत जानकारी</string>
    <string name="select_profile">प्रोफ़ाइल छवि चुनें</string>
    <string name="select_buss">व्यवसाय की छवि चुनें</string>
    <string name="sole_owner">क्या आप स्टोर के मालिक हैं?</string>
    <string name="proceed">आगे बढ़े</string>
    <string name="buss_info">व्यवसाय जानकारी</string>
    <string name="shop_location">दुकान का स्थान</string>
    <string name="bussloc">व्यवसाय का स्थान</string>
    <string name="login">लॉग इन करें</string>
    <string name="register_new_user">रजिस्टर करें</string>
    <string name="quote">रजिस्टर करें और भुगतान स्वीकार करना शुरू करें !!</string>
    <string name="accept_UPI">UPI के माध्यम से स्वीकार करें</string>
    <string name="accept_bank">बैंक खाते के माध्यम से स्वीकार करें</string>
    <string name="mark_shop_location">अपनी दुकान का स्थान चिह्नित करें</string>
    <string name="maxcredit">अधिकतम क्रेडिट(अधिकतम कुल भुगतान आप रु में चाहते हैं)</string>
    <string name="transactions">लेनदेन का सारांश</string>
    <string name="netamt">निवल राशि</string>
    <string name="donations">दान</string>
    <string name="getotp">ओ.टी.पी. प्राप्त करें</string>
    <string name="verifyotp">ओ.टी.पी. सत्यापित करें</string>
    <string name="enterphn">10 अंकों का फोन नंबर दर्ज करें</string>
    <string name="enterotp">ओटीपी दर्ज करें</string>
    <string name="entervpa">vpa दर्ज करें(आभासी भुगतान पता)</string>
    <string name="firstname">पहला नाम</string>
    <string name="lastname">सरनेम</string>
    <string name="address">पता</string>
    <string name="owner">क्या आप स्टोर के मालिक हैं?</string>
    <string name="bussname">व्यवास्यक नाम</string>
    <string name="busstype">व्यापार प्रकार</string>
    <string name="bussaddr">व्यावसायिक पता</string>
    <string name="enteracc">अपना खाता नंबर दर्ज करें</string>
    <string name="ifsc">ifsc कोड दर्ज करें</string>
    <string name="agree">हाँ मैं सहमत हूँ</string>
    <string name="change">बदलें</string>
    <string name="nodon">अभी तक कोई दान नहीं</string>
    <string name="transaction">आपको यहां अपना हालिया लेन-देन मिलेगा</string>
    <string name="mou">यह समझौता ज्ञापन: \n "DaanCorona" के बीच सहयोग के लिए शर्तें स्थापित करता है: इसमें मोबाइल एप्लिकेशन, ऑनलाइन वेब-एप्लिकेशन और दी जा रही सेवा का सार ("ऐप" या "प्लेटफॉर्म" या "सेवा" के रूप में संदर्भित) शामिल है। )। \ n "(व्यवसाय का नाम)": इसमें कोरोनाोना मंच पर साइन-अप करने के उद्देश्य से व्यवसाय और व्यवसाय के हितधारक - मालिक, कर्मचारी और जैसे ("व्यवसाय" के रूप में संदर्भित) शामिल हैं। और निम्न पर अधोहस्ताक्षरी द्वारा सहमति व्यक्त की जा रही है। \ n (ए) अवधि: \ n दोनों पक्षों द्वारा हस्ताक्षर किए जाने के बाद, यह समझौता ज्ञापन (__ / __ / ____) पर शुरू होगा और तब तक रहेगा (__ / __) / ____)। यह समझौता ज्ञापन वसीयत में है और इस प्रकार दोनों पक्षों के सक्षम अधिकारियों की आपसी सहमति से इसे संशोधित किया जा सकता है। इस प्रकार समझौता ज्ञापन की अवधि को आपसी सहमति से बढ़ाया या घटाया जा सकता है। DaanCorona से \ n (B) वितरण: \ n इस समझौता ज्ञापन पर हस्ताक्षर करने के बाद, DaanCorona इन डिलिवरेबल्स का वादा करेगा: \ n (1) प्लेटफ़ॉर्म पर व्यवसाय के लिए एक सार्वजनिक प्रोफ़ाइल बनाना।</string>
</resources>
